[CHATTERING ON TV]
(Leonard:)Did I miss anything?
Did they kick Giselle off?
(Raj:)Not yet, but her underwater photo shoot
was an embarrassment.
(Howard:)Sadly, Mrs. Giselle Wolowitz
is sensitive to chlorine.
(Howard:)Lucky for her I like my fashion models
pruny and bug-eyed.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, the food's here.
Oh, there's the house.
(Raj:)Freeze frame, freeze frame.
- What are you doing?
- Marking the positions and landmarks...
(Raj:)...so we can find the house
of the supermodels.
(Leonard:)- Why?
- Isn't it obvious?
(Howard:)Every week they kick out
a beautiful girl...
(Howard:)...making her feel unwanted
and without self-esteem.
(Howard:)A.k.a. the future Mrs. Howard Wolowitz.
- Is my hamburger medium-well?
- Yes.
- Dill slices, not sweet?